我来煮点咖啡好吗,Jane?
Shall I make some coffee,Jane?
这是个好主意,Charlotte.
That's a good idea, Charlotte.
咖啡好了,
It's ready.
你要放点奶吗?
Do you want any milk?
请稍加一点.
Just a little, please.
加些糖怎么样?
What about some sugar?
两茶匙行吗?
Two teaspoonfuls?
不,再少一些.
No, less than that.
请放一勺儿半.
One and a half teaspoonfuls, please.
那对我足够了.
That's enough for me.
太好了.
That was very nice.
你要再来点吗?
Would you like some more?
好的,请再来一点.
Yes, please.
我还想抽枝烟.
I'd like a cigarette, too.
可以给我一枝吗?
May I have one?
当然可以.
Of course.
我想那个盒子里有一些.
I think there are a few in that box.
我恐怕盒子是空的.
I'm afraid it's empty.
真遗憾!
What a pity!
没关系.
It doesn't matter.
那就吃块饼干吧.
Have a biscuit instead.
多吃点,少抽点!
Eat more and smoke less!
这是极好的忠告啊!
That's very good advice!